He makes forever!
The captain's square off!
The final combat round!
The battle has ended, and you know what that means!
Time to choose your bounty!
Tough luck, but you should have seen this one coming!
I missed you, Choppy!
Don't you ever leave me again!
Robin!
We'll work something out, Doctor. Don't cry.
Hey, we're kinda running out of options here.
How are you gonna get us out of this?
I got this under control.
We'll have a third day V-back fight and win all three rounds!
Now you want to go for three?
I don't think so.
Let me ask you a question, boy.
Do you know why the Foxy Pirates are the strongest of the strong, the best of the best?
You really think you're the best, huh?
Then why did you lose to us twice?
Ah, you're splitting hairs here. Come on.
Listen, you're asking for a third fight in a row, but we had five three-coin games with the Fang Frog Pirates today before we even ran into you saps!
Now I don't like to back down from a challenge, but my crew is spent. They're tired. They're injured. They've been giving it their best all day long.
Beg us for a third match all you want. But I'd be a fool to put my crew at risk like that. Being the best there is takes more than just strength.
You have to know when it's time to keep fighting and when it's time to quit and call it a day!
Uh...
Uh, what? So impressed you don't know what to say?
You gotta be kidding me. First you brag about how strong you are, then we're supposed to feel sorry for you?
Poor Foxy. He's so strong he has to cheat to win. It's not his fault he challenged us.
Even if we end up winning the final round, what should we do? It's not like we can get Chopper and Robin back. How can we choose? And what if we have to leave both of them with those losers?
I'm not leaving anybody. I'll make it happen somehow.
Somehow isn't good enough. We need a plan.
I'm getting sick of dealing with these guys. How about I just chop them up instead?
I don't like them either, but let's try to keep the bloodshed to a minimum, okay?
Hey, boss. I have a little proposition for you.
Huh?
Instead of one person, let's bet five this time.
Are you crazy? We already lost two!
Wait. It's alright. Let her handle this.
Go on. I'm all ears.
The point of the game is to take the crew members you want from the other team, right?
Well, we want Robin and Chopper. And if we can't have them both, then there's no point in us having a crew at all.
Huh?
In fact, you don't even need to risk five of your crewmates. We'll put everything on the line just for those two.
In other words, if you beat us, you get the rest of our crew. All five members in one shot.
What do you say? Sounds like a pretty good deal if you ask me.
This girl has some serious guts to try and bargain with me. She might make a good crew member. And those two are some of the strongest fighters I've ever seen. Even their snipers seem to have some useful tools at his disposal.
And their captain, well, his 100 million very bounty speaks for hisself.
Yes! You have a deal! But what's the fun in betting only two crewmates? Make it 500.
That's right! 500 of my men in addition to the two you asked for!
Are you serious?
Uh, you sure about that?
Our boss is throwing down the gauntlet with his dreaded 500-man bat! Well, Shawhat, what do you say?
What would we do with 500 people? That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard!
Shut up!
Don't ruin this for us when he already agreed to the important part!
But we couldn't fit 500 people on the merry if we tried!
It doesn't matter if it's five people or 500 people as long as we're able to get Robin and Chopper back!
Uh, right.
So, do you accept?
Yeah! You bet I do!
By the way, since your team doesn't actually have 500 members to bet, you'll have to pay us with your descendants if you lose the match!
In other words, not only you, but your children, grandchildren, great-grandchildren, and whoever else it takes to make up 500 people will swear their loyalty to the Foxy Pirates and join our crew!
Our children, too?
Hi, Daddy!
Aw, come here, sweetie!
I don't know about this, you guys. It's kind of a weird deal, don't you think?
It's too late to be getting cold feet now. And besides, it doesn't matter as long as we win. Give it 100%, Luffy!
Yeah! Leave it to me!
Hef! Hef! Hef! Hef! Hef! Hef!
I hate to bust your bubble there, rubber boy, but just as a fair warning, nobody has ever been able to beat me in the combat round!
You may be captain now, but you'll be swabbing my dick soon!
Oh, yeah? You think you can beat me in a fight?
Hef! Hef! Hef! Hef! Maybe so, and maybe not.
Oh, and maybe not. But this isn't a fight, my boy. It's a game.
One, two, three, four! Who's the man that's gonna score? Foxy!
Yeah, sure! We finally arrived at the combat round, but before we start, we must decide on the battlefield. The two competitors spin this unbiased cannon, and wherever it stops, is the place where they'll do combat!
The match hasn't even started yet, and you guys are cheating already?!
There you have it! The battlefield has been set! And would you look at that! By sheer coincidence, it's on the deck of the Sexy Foxy!
Oh, now you're just rubbing it in, you little liar!
Moving right along, let's explain the rules of combat!
Everything within 50 meters of where the cannonball landed is considered part of the battlefield. In other words, it's a hundred meter wide circle measuring from the center of the ship!
Weapons and anything else found inside the designated battlefield are allowed. However, outside crew members are strictly forbidden from entering the ship! Knock your opponent out of bounds and you win the match! Simple as that!
Also, as long as you're in the circle fighting in the air or water is fine!
F-O-X-Y Foxy!
While we're busy preparing for the main event, Porch's lovely flower cheerleaders are performing on the stage!
If that's not your thing, you can also check out a warm-up match being held on the front of the ship!
And as always, our Association of Stulls is selling a limited-edition Davey-back-fight merchandise, so be sure to check that out as well!
Nobody wants your junk, just start the match already!
One, please!
And here you go, fellas, two limited-edition Foxy pins!
Haven't you seen enough of his dumb face?
We're ready!
Where's your captain at?
He's right there!
Now take him before he buys something else!
So what are you getting mad about this time?
What do you think?
I'm mad at you idiots for not taking this seriously!
If everybody sits back and lets Foxy run the show, we're gonna get cheated out of our whole crew!
He's running the show because he has the manpower to do it.
His guys outnumber us a hundred to one.
Exactly!
That's why we can't let him have more!
Luffy won't lose!
Why don't we just sit back and enjoy the show for once?
Now!
You go on ahead!
I'll run and get us some drinks, okay?
Hey!
You two!
Come here for a sec!
I've got something for ya!
Voila!
Some snacks for the show!
How much?
Huh?
Free of charge!
Oh, how kind of you!
Oh, yeah!
Even if Luffy loses the last round, at least we'll all be a part of the same crew again!
Sure beats having everyone split up, don't you think?
Well, yes, that may be so.
But even if we are together, the captain won't be our captain anymore.
Actually, he won't be a captain at all, since the whole crew will be serving under Foxy.
I'm gonna be the-
King of the Pirates!
You better start swapping those deck suckers!
Yes, sir!
But that won't happen, cause Luffy's gonna win, right?
He has to, cause we have to!
And I don't know how Toll!
I won't think!
Well, yes, that may be so!
But even if we are together, the captain won't be our captain anymore.
Actually, he won't be a captain at all, since the whole crew will be serving under Foxy.
I'm gonna be the-
King of the Pirates!
Fifi!
You better start swapping those deck suckers!
Yes, sir!
But that won't happen, cause Luffy's gonna win, right?
because we have our own adventure
that we gotta finish together no matter what.
I'm sure that is exactly what the captain is thinking.
Are you kidding me?
Why do I have to pay so much for your crappy popcorn and cola?
If you don't like the price, how about you don't buy it?
Give me 50% off!
Get out of here, you!
What's all that stuff?
This is the dressing room.
You gotta wear boxing gloves, but pretty much anything else goes.
This is awesome!
This place is more like a costume shop than a dressing room, you know?
Man, I can't pick a favorite.
Do you think it'd be okay if I just wore all of it at once?
Hey, what about this? Am I cool now?
No.
This is it.
That cannon means the preparations are complete.
So if the opening entertainment could please leave the stage.
Thank you!
And now it's time for the main event!
The fighters are in place, and the bell is ready to sound!
Grab a seat and the spectator stands before it's too late!
Now that's odd.
It's cloudy all of a sudden.
Nami!
I'm back!
Where are you?
Only got one bucket of popcorn?
Hope you plan to share.
Today we have a real treat, ladies and gentlemen!
A captain versus captain showdown!
Yeah!
You can't shut up!
Yeah, better get your eyes checked!
First, in the left corner!
We have a reigning Davy Mac champion!
A man among men who never turns down a challenge!
That boasts a legendary combat record of 920 wins and zero losses!
Our one and only boss!
The Silver Fox Foxes!
You listen up, Luffy!
A captain versus captain showdown!
Yeah!
You can't shut up, Luffy!
Yeah, better get your eyes checked!
First, in the left corner!
We have a reigning Davy Mac champion!
A man among men who never turns down a challenge!
That boasts a legendary combat record of 920 wins and zero losses!
Our one and only boss!
The Silver Fox Foxes!
You listen up, Luffy!
And you listen up good!
You ain't your old self no more!
You put that boy to bed!
And now you're gone and woken up a man!
Just like that hairstyle's woken up your wild side!
Since the dawn of time, man has wondered if the champion makes the afro or the afro makes the champion!
But that's a question even modern science can't answer!
Now listen, with that afro on your head, your fists are weapons of mass destruction!
Strawhead's too scared to come out!
I bet he ran away!
All right, Pops, let's rock!
Oh, yeah!
And in the right corner, our challenger!
Hailing from the east blue with a tiny crew of only seven and a massive 100 million fairy bounty!
The rubber wonder they call Straw Hat!
Monkey Day!
Luffy!
Yeah!
Wow! Luffy is sporting a larger than life afro with a personality to match!
Yeah! Looking sharp, buddy!
That's messed up!
Wow! Luffy's cooler than ever!
I agree!
Both fighters have entered the battlefield and look like they're ready to rumble!
Now that Luffy has turned in his straw hat for a mighty afro, does he have the power to protect the pride of his crew and unborn children alike?
Ooh!
Or will Foxy's undefeated fist strip him of all his hopes and dreams?
Only time will tell as this fateful final round of the Daveyback fight explodes into action!
But first, a word from our sponsors!
Hey, Straw Hat! I'm really diggin' the new look!
I mean, Usank!
Pull a quick bait with your left!
Then slap that gym with a golden uppercut!
Yeah!
So funky!
I can feel that jar of lighting a fire in my soul!
You see, this is what happens when you leave Luffy alone with Usank.
Couldn't he try to show some dignity for once?
Hey, not too shabby!
Sometimes you gotta unleash the beast to win!
Not that you have any chance against me!
You might be the champ, but this one's got some bite!
He's out of sight!
You best get ready to fight!
Cause this one-two punch is gonna give you a rip!
Alright, Corner Man!
It's time to take your sideshow to the sidelines!
But I was really getting my groove on!
You can't make me leave already!
Manager!
Out!
Along with the show!
And since I'm not needed here either, I'll be on my merry way!
Let's get this thing started!
Huh?
What the...
The stands are moving!
Whoa!
Cool!
I gotta get chairs like that on my ship!
Feef!
Now then, Luffy!
What do you say you and I have a little fun?
This whole ship is our playground, after all!
Feel free to go as wild as you like!
Don't worry!
We have plenty of skilled shipwrights to clean up after our mess!
Feef!
Now the opponents face off atop the fabulous figurehead of the sexy Foxy!
Which was chosen by sheer coincidence, of course!
What kind of fearsome flying fists will be unfurled today?
Get a blast!
You can't let that winning streak stop now!
Luffy!
Don't lose!
That's all that matters!
Just watch out for his beam, okay?
Excitement fills the stands in the final seconds before the match!
It's Blunder or Be Plundered with Foxy's infamous 500-man wager raising the stakes sky-high!
Will Foxy seize six generations of Straw Hats?
Luffy!
Go Plus!
It's the Silver Slow Slow Slugger versus the Gum Gum Gatling Gun!
This is a one-round bout with no time limit!
As long as they stay in bounds, anything goes!
The fighters are ready!
And there goes the bell!
Yeah!
No!
Slow Slow Bee!
My arm is fast, but my fist is all slow!
You don't expect me to be afraid of a rubber hose, do you?
Gimme a sec!
Come back!
Slow Slow Bee!
I fooled you!
What are you?
Flow slow beam!
Luffy!
Wow, he's floating.
I guess that means he falls slow too.
I told him to watch out for that.
Why won't he listen to me?
Man, talk about pathetic!
Come on, boss, put him out of his misery!
Wait!
Oh, no!
I know there's no time limit, but come on!
Why don't you spare us both and give up?
No way!
Nine tails arrived!
Oh!
Our boss unleashes his signature attack right off the bat!
Straw Hat is helpless to fight back!
This is crazy. He's not budging an inch.
No, look closely. He's just moving in slow motion.
Consider that a preview of what's to come.
Though to your credit, it seems like you can take a punch pretty well.
Fortunately, I've got plenty of other tricks up my sleeve.
Come back here.
Well, your 30 seconds are about off.
Uh, what?
The beam wore off. He's falling overboard.
Luffy!
That slow, slow beam is gonna give me more trouble than I thought.
Wow, beams sure are cool, huh?
Still, I gotta be more careful where I stretch my arms now.
Where'd that jerk run off to anyway?
I will let you sneak up on me with your beam, split head!
Come out and fight like a man!
I understand your frustration, but don't take it out on the ears!
Did he use his beam?
Welcome to the sexy Foxy Rubber Boy!
That was a dirty trick!
He got me!
Just calm down for a second, will ya?
Can't you see I'm trying to show you some hospitality here?
Those cannonballs are moving in slow-mo, too.
Well, if you can ride on one, then so can I!
Careful, kid! I wouldn't touch that one if I were you!
Ah, and that one, too!
Beep!
Can't say I didn't warn you!
What was that?
I can't make out anything from where we're sitting!
Hey, Robin!
Can you tell what's going on from up there?
No! All I can see is smoke!
This sucks!
What's his problem, anyway?
If he keeps this up, he's gonna sink his own ship!
I'll sink you first!
Slow, slow, foxy-faced bomb cannon!
Ah! Creepy!
Creepy!
Huh? Oh, they're pins!
They sure are a lot bigger than the one I bought, though.
Of course we're bigger, stupid!
That's because we're bombs, not pins!
Wait, what? Did you say bomb?
Why is a bomb talking?
I'm the real thing, that's why!
My punches weren't quite doing the trick.
So I upgraded my gloves!
See?
Oh, and fair warning, those bombs are about to go off!
Yeah! Body blue! Body blue!
Oh, it's Usopp.
Hey, what's going on with the fight down there?
I don't have a clue.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, no!
That looks bad!
I don't have a clue!
I'm gonna be there!
No!
You're a good one!
I'm gonna be there!
Oh, no!
We'll be right back.
Talk more boxing!
On the next, Wood Piece!
Full blast slow slow onslaught versus invulnerable Luffy!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Nope, I am!
Hey!